

# **Denis Kufakov (Loza)**

# FRONTEND developer | HTML | CSS | JS | TS | React

Email: denisloza.git@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/denis-loza Github: github.com/DenisLoza

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a front-end developer with 2 years of experience building SPAs using React and TypeScript.

I have experience in various industries, such as the creation of professional media content, technical support for payment systems and scientific work in the field of biotechnology.

#### **SKILLS**

#### • TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Programming: JavaScript, TypeScript, DOM, React;
- Testing & Linters: Unit tests, Jest, ESLint;
- Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Flex, Bootstrap;
- Continuous Integration: Git, GitActions;
- Media: professional photo and video editing (Photoshop, FinalCut);
  - Webpack, Command line, Linux.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

FreeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design (April 2021)

#### **EDUCATION**

Centria University of Applied Sciences Bachelor of engineering, Information technology August 2023 - ongoing Kokkola, Finland.

### Hexlet

FrontEnd Developer Oct 2021 - Jan 2023 E-Learning provider. Helsinki, Finland.

#### **NBCPMA**

Master's Biotech engineer 1998 - 2003 Moscow, Russian Federation.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Russian: Native English: Intermediate

# **HOBBIES**

For me, sports and music go closely with programming, both of those fields help to stay creative and attentive. So, in my spare time, I do sport and play guitar! Also, as an active person, I like long walks in nature.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# My Pet Projects:

# Social Net project (SPA) React

GitHub: https://github.com/DenisLoza/SocialXXI The layout of the project was implemented by me without the use of templates.

I implemented demo limited functionality of the main page of the user and the messages page.

Design similar to VKontakte.

Implemented functionality:

- \* Posting a message on the home page;
- \* Jumping by category "Friends Main";
- \* Sending a private message to a friend;

#### TodoList project (SPA) React

GitHub: https://github.com/DenisLoza/TodoListXXI I implemented the following features:

- \* Adding a new list and new tasks to the list;
- \* Marking completed tasks;
- \* Deleting tasks and task lists;
- \* Switching between cases (active, completed and deleted)
- \* Renaming tasks & lists (editable span).

# <u>Media content production's - Entrepreneur</u>

Jul 2013 - Sep 2022, St. Petersburg, Russia

I was in charge of pre-production (professional photo and video shooting) and post-production (processing and editing of media content).

More than 500 satisfied customers!

- I got a good Business-to-Consumer experience;
- built long-term and trusting relationships with more than 100 clients;
- I have developed the ability to achieve excellent results.

# <u>Technical Director - Single settlement center</u>

May 2010 - Mar 2013, Yekaterinburg, Russia

Information technology, system integration, cash management services.

I was engaged in administration and service control of special software and hardware (Linux).

- installed and expanded the network of payment terminals from 0 to 200;
- integrated a network of terminals in 7 cities;
- due to the stable operation of the payment network and reached 20,000 transactions per day.

Working in the company has significantly increased performance on the highest technical equipment and development rates to a large regional network.